(Penny:)So, you just left them alone
playing games in your house?
(Dr Lorvis:)Well, they seemed happy and...
(Man:)I thought
that would give me time
(Dr Lorvis:)for you and I to get
to know each other better.
(Dr Lorvis:)That was before we met.
(Amy:)We all have a past.
(Penny:)Doc, you've got to see what
you're doing
is-is a little creepy.
(Dr Lorvis:)You sound just
like Sigourney Weaver
(Dr Lorvis:)when I followed her
into a restroom.
(Penny:)Okay, you can't
just go chasing after
(Penny:)every girl who's nice to you.
(Dr Lorvis:)Well, that's not
what Sheldon says.
(Dr Lorvis:)And he seems to know
his way around the ladies.
(cell phone ringing)
Hey, Leonard. Guess who's back!
Dr. Lorvis!
(Penny(on phone):)Yeah. You care to join us?
What?!
(Penny(on phone):)You locked them
in your basement?!
(Dr Lorvis:)Well, they're,
they're not locked in.
(Dr Lorvis:)The door just sticks.
(Penny:)Okay, so how do they unstick it?
(Dr Lorvis:)They'd need the key.